// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "This is that which contains all life on earth.",
    answer: "b. biosphere",
    options: [
      "a. ecosystem",
      "b. biosphere",
      "c. community",
      "d. earth",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "This is a chemical structure consisting of two or more atoms.",
    answer: "d. molecule",
    options: [
      "a. atomic number",
      "b. mixture",
      "c. solution",
      "d. molecule",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "This is the fundamental unit of structure and function among organisms.",
    answer: "a. cell",
    options: [
      "a. cell",
      "b. tissue",
      "c. organ",
      "d. organ system",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "This is a type of cell that lacks a true nucleus and membrane-bound organelles.",
    answer: "a. prokaryotic",
    options: [
      "a. prokaryotic",
      "b. eukaryotic",
      "c. sex cell",
      "d. muscle cell",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "This is the form of that genetic materials take in chromosomes.",
    answer: "a. DNA",
    options: [
      "a. DNA",
      "b. RNA",
      "c. Gene",
      "d. Chromatid",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "This is the entire collection of genetic instruction that an organism inherits.",
    answer: "a. genome",
    options: [
      "a. genome",
      "b. gene expression",
      "c. genomics",
      "d. alleles",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Producers in a food chain or web are _______ in nature.",
    answer: "d. photosynthetic",
    options: [
      "a. heterotrophic",
      "b. singular",
      "c. single-celled",
      "d. photosynthetic",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "He is the father of evolution.",
    answer: "c. Charles Darwin",
    options: [
      "a. Alexander Graham Bell",
      "b. Copernicus",
      "c. Charles Darwin",
      "d. Gregor Mendel",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "This is the ideal duration of pregnancy among humans.",
    answer: "d. 38 weeks",
    options: [
      "a. 32 weeks",
      "b. 34 weeks",
      "c. 36 weeks",
      "d. 38 weeks",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is a type of sexual reproduction?",
    answer: "a. hermaphroditism",
    options: [
      "a. hermaphroditism",
      "b. fragmentation",
      "c. budding",
      "d. parthenogenesis",
    ],
  },
];
